</salt>

School of applied technology



Izabela Szymczyk

Open-minded and creative Full Stack JavaScript
Developer from Poland living in Oslo, Norway. Finance
and Accountancy graduate, experienced in different
industries and running my own business. Now, I am
professionally fulfilling my passion - programming. I
have an analytical mind which I trained during
economic studies, but I also have sensitivity and
artistic skills. Privately, Scandinavian landscapes
and van life lover.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

General

JavaScript TypeScript

Backend

NodeJS ExpressJS REST GraphQL MongoDB/PostgreSQL

Frontend

React
Redux
React Native
Next.js
Webpack
HTML
jQuery
CSS/SASS/styled-components

Tools and technologies

Visual Studio Code
Handlebars/Mustache
Mocha/Jest/TDD
Docker
Git / GitHub / GitHub Actions
AWS
Cloud Platforms (MongoDB Atlas,
ElephantSQL, Netlify, Heroku,
Contentful)
Agile work methods
Postman
Figma

Links

Linkedin Github Portfolio

Languages

Polish - Native English - Fluent Norwegian - Beginner

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Full Stack JavaScript - School of Applied Technology </salt>

Intensive three month training program for full stack web development with a focus on TDD, mob programming, and applied learning.

The Web Developer Bootcamp 2022 Udemy - Colt Steele <u>certificate</u>

The Modern React Bootcamp (Hooks, Context, NextJS, Router) UDEMY - Colt Steele certificate

Bachelor of Accounting and Finance - Maria Curie-Sklodowska University (Poland)

10.2013 - 06.2016 accounting of enterprises and Institutions

XXIII High School in Lublin (Poland)

09.2010 - 05.2013

IT & Mathematical bilingual profile

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Owner - Fenari

02.2019 - 10.2020

implementing and achieving business goals in my own service activity - beauty industry.

Insurance Agent - Mendel Insurance

05.2018 - 12.2019

Administration of insurance contracts and sale insurance products.

E-commerce sales specialist - PHU Top Stock

10.2016 - 05.2018

Operation of IT software supporting e-commerce sales. Creating product descriptions, graphic design. Product database management.

Shift Manager/Salesman - Drugstore Natura

10.2015 - 07.2016

Teamwork management, active implementation of sales plans.